[Music]
[音乐]
life sciences
生命科学
the criticism of open source and access
对开源和访问的批评
management solutions applications
管理解决方案应用
community developer community 100
社区开发者社区100
worst-case account at the disco
迪斯科舞厅的最坏情况
Sound integrates facebook twitter user
声音整合了Facebook Twitter用户
management support directory services
管理支持目录服务
that you connect becomes the existence
你连接成为存在
the ski club is highly custom too
滑雪俱乐部也是高度定制的
I'm coming you luxor
我要来你卢克索
the night is thus heidi extensible that
夜晚是海蒂可扩展的
you can not teach ski club new tricks at
你不能教滑雪俱乐部的新技巧
Configuration core animation of the
配置核心动画
protocol integration before
之前的协议集成
block i have to get some of its torque
块我必须得到一些扭矩
on demand is an element container
按需是元素容器
clients general settings like you have
像您一样的客户常规设置
So configuration file integration often
所以配置文件经常集成
Set of social ox identity providers
一组社会牛身份提供商
already prix conficker trio lily to
已经把conficker三人百合奖给了
configure york exists angels
配置约克存在天使
simpson maybe a book that is still
辛普森也许是一本书
the night
夜晚
the connect of summer to connect with
夏天的连接
your tax is integration mcsorley
你的税是整合麦克索利
plugins user federation providers
插件用户联合提供者
Uzbek exposures from proprietary user
乌兹别克斯坦专有用户的风险敞口
data base is then not an of key
那么数据库不是关键
management public at coffee and
管理公众在咖啡和
croissants differentiation operation
新月形面包的分化操作
identity provider and user federation
身份提供者和用户联盟
often get mixed em up provider effects
经常会混淆供应商效果
for the gpu we login to external
对于gpu，我们登录到外部
elaborate saying all this as well
也要详细说明
external login page that the user for
用户用于的外部登录页面
the upper hand eustacchio block in pages
页面中上位的尤斯塔基奥块
with data from here belongs to external
来自这里的数据属于外部
service extremely lure page pictogram
服务极度诱人的页面象形图
that okay
没关系
has with the configuration of nicole
与妮可的配置
fetting trade it for the study of
交易以研究
several things first thing i want to
我想做的第一件事
show you is the thing going on in presto
表明你是事前发生的事情
Thursdays whiskey club friends since
自星期四以来，威士忌俱乐部的朋友们
have you are sorry the pictures locations
您对图片的位置感到抱歉吗
in the live view, implement a
在实时视图中，实施
flight in front of god password europe working
在上帝密码欧洲工作前飞行
with the working for god password
与工作神密码
Mechanisms justin mapletoft compliment
贾斯汀·马普莱托夫赞美机制
customized 42 looks like a customized
定制的42看起来像定制的
content sales at change log in
更改时的内容销售登录
the user account management of the title
标题的用户帐户管理
professional clubs managed applications apps
专业俱乐部托管的应用程序
mobile apps or websites lux and
行动应用程式或网站lux和
thunderstorm unique client the smallest
雷暴唯一客户最小
business rules and application of client
客户的业务规则和应用
level
水平
you can go on course so gentleman
你可以继续前进，先生
level global global review that includes
级别的全球全球审核，其中包括
the new identity provider active
新的身份提供者处于活动状态
directory access returns the most
目录访问返回最多
interesting trapped here is on course and
有趣的是这里正在进行中
profile information
个人资料信息
[Music]
[音乐]
manager views on the legend of the
经理对传奇的看法
seeker management software password
搜寻器管理软件密码
management information about what
关于什么的管理信息
happened related events login login
发生相关事件登录登录
immediately but you can access information
立即但您可以访问信息
[Music]
[音乐]
the horizontal templates template
水平模板模板
engine
发动机
june to external title the way this is
6月外部标题的方式是
your stage of course you can eat your
你当然可以吃你的
own life technologies is the album work
自己的生活技术是专辑的工作
because of you had used to james
因为你已经习惯了
module system in oslo thing is that the us
奥斯陆的模块系统是美国
weekly first place youtube-user
每周第一名youtube用户
information pages of convenience of st
便利的信息页面
and just as user access client users
就像用户访问客户端用户一样
of admin rest api of programmatic great
编程性的admin rest api的说明
that is also immediately the vsk 1 that is so
那也马上就是vsk 1
a base youtube conficker kluck
一个基本的youtube conficker kluck
instance before people event
事前事件实例
Infrastructure from youtube on the spot
youtube上的基础设施
events in text form or in the program for example
以文本形式或程序中的事件为例
custom extension to any messaging data
自定义扩展到任何消息传递数据
integration connectivity eustace
集成连接性
July completely cluster on engines
7月完全聚集在引擎上
Connected again in bonds groups say
再次联系债券集团说
played information configuration so that
播放信息配置，以便
the architecture architecture often the
架构经常
underlying architect on the club
俱乐部的基础架构师
urges
冲动
next appointment the next salimi in
下次约会下一个salimi
the deponie works for web applications
小矮人适用于Web应用程序
to work for mobile apps and desktop apps
适用于移动应用程序和桌面应用程序
and a half men in my guitar post
我的吉他室里有一个半人
Until the thing is also a confession to
直到事情也告白
club out provides support for single
俱乐部外出为单身人士提供支持
what you can lockout in the form of
您可以锁定的形式
application a diss lockout is a
应用程序锁定是一个
dropper gate to other applications
通往其他应用的滴管
club of gore source application scanning
戈尔俱乐部源码应用程序扫描
to decide whether or not to react
决定是否做出反应
the lok authors of my never wrote down
我的乐作家从未写下
ever really and global lookout and that
曾经真正的全球监视，那
disneyland gets many factors
迪士尼乐园有很多因素
that can make it work now yes the
现在可以使它工作了，是的
politics so that the vignettes and we used
政治，使小插曲和我们使用
to access the application server browser
访问应用程序服务器浏览器
by john cage the user interface
通过john cage的用户界面
to lure credentials
诱骗凭证
with copy in front of the club domain lay with
俱乐部域前面的副本与
eur then knock general director central
欧元然后敲敲中央总监
park west differences with news of the
公园西差异与新闻
information from expectations and public
来自期望和公众的信息
reference to
参考
the temperature is content content
温度就是内容
delivery and reference to have decided
交付和参考已决定
to make this content can be used
使该内容可以使用
effects of pop michael jackson
流行迈克尔·杰克逊的影响
the shortlist in the engine of management
管理引擎中的入围者
of the user access applications discovered
发现的用户访问应用程序
that you have much longer lift in the
你的举升时间更长
harbor the unique client client that can
拥有可以
be used for mobile applications
用于移动应用
application that i want to the teachers
我想要给老师的申请
once in a while
偶尔
because an e-mail with triflex is open
因为打开了带有triflex的电子邮件
Increase source and speaking
增加来源和口语
the almost lane street and the signature
几乎是小巷的街道和签名
component basics the four in front of sony one
组件基础知识，索尼的四大要素
code information
代码信息
this is how the windsors effect of
这就是温莎效应
reference to the public key public and
引用公钥public和
the small side lukas engelke
小边卢卡斯·恩格尔克
because you have the actual pilot john key
因为你有实际的飞行员约翰·基
value persia the secret claims for which
价值波斯的秘密主张
some of the most enteist so the board
一些最有远见的人，所以董事会
first as head of customer value path of
首先是客户价值路径的负责人
users to transform
用户转型
information displays fotos.de display
信息显示fotos.de显示
information like my photos
像我的照片一样的信息
broad so that basic works just want to
广泛，以便基础作品只想
make sure you back and stay just not
确保你回来并留下来
received a reference to publish what we
收到了发布我们的内容的参考
Can integrated cowbells
可以整合牛铃
applicationserver ski club province song
applicationserver滑雪俱乐部省歌
integration options for openid connect
openid connect的集成选项
in the shape of skepticism
持怀疑态度
the map-report integration article
地图报告集成文章
province of jawa landscape like for security
霍巴省风景如出于安全考虑
spring puta planes of light fourth
Spring 普塔轻第四架
based on for many as of yet container
基于许多容器
center like but maintain javascript
中心喜欢，但维护javascript
based integration process en plaine
基于标准的集成过程
javascript angela in kiel ots
javascript在基尔ots中的angela
smart integration fund apps or
智能整合基金应用或
desktop apps that simply connect
只需连接即可的桌面应用
the software fx is integration of using
该软件FX是使用集成
the box integration projects nike
盒子整合项目耐克
gatekeeper also proxys or ford connect
网守还代理或福特连接
protocol interaction and grace kelly
协议交互和宽限期
with the elaborate information
详尽的信息
information
信息
the author integrations webserver apache
作者集成Web服务器apache
engine expo on whether to connect and
引擎博览会上是否连接和
summer badzinski monastery
夏天Badzinski修道院
You can also plan to connect
您还可以计划连接
on samuel integration suite iworks
在samuel集成套件iworks上
the team democracy with outlook
有远见的团队民主
integration server environment for
的集成服务器环境
applications with the sec and services
SEC和服务的应用程序
that i can do it like it's ok to all off
我可以做到，就像一切都可以
you get back to the kentucky and he's
你回到肯塔基，他是
back list of today is ok to reason data
今天的清单可以确定数据
So wants to be accessed by another
所以想被另一个人访问
application and that is just a spring
应用程序，这只是一个 Spring
mbc service integration kloppp-elf left
mbc服务集成kloppp-elf左
application suite local based
基于本地的应用程序套件
application javascript based 2
基于Java的应用程序2
they could us on the existing
他们可以在现有的我们
that provider for the application the
该应用程序的提供商
token 1 success from the application here
从这里的应用程序获得令牌1成功
as well as access account values
以及访问帐户值
developed project for the application
为应用开发的项目
It was a lockout in Bonn application
这是波恩申请中的封锁
lockout with lockout both churches that
封锁与封锁两个教堂
is today global workforce study back
今天是全球劳动力研究
and application of the mainstream secret
主流秘密的研究与应用
kikuyu application variant of the adapter
适配器的kikuyu应用程序变体
repository play off to le mans
勒芒勒芒库
the collection of cold spring security
收集冷泉安全
and the offspring good starter of the panel
和小组的后代
and just get out of fuel 1 configuration
并摆脱燃料1的配置
so just add water application excel is
所以只需加水应用excel是
that's just amazing jump arrest
那简直是惊人的跳跳
order to make it work
为了使其工作
configuration in the application whines
在应用程序配置中抱怨
the on servers
服务器上
let's play scales with one
让我们一起玩一个音阶
conficker for access constraints like
混淆访问限制，例如
of the eurocup can only be accessed
只能访问欧元杯
through you that makes the front and
通过你，使正面和
integration server be from the
集成服务器来自
integration
积分
christa battistini ski clubs
克里斯塔·巴蒂斯蒂尼滑雪俱乐部
configuration security in a simple java
简单Java中的配置安全性
configuration plain text web security
配置纯文本Web安全
Contractor configuration configuration
承包商配置配置
so is the confetti flew and
五彩纸屑也飞了
workarounds configuration problems
解决方法配置问题
the information from plock provided by
plock提供的信息，由
example here to client the basecaps the
此处以客户为例
progress template template of
进度模板
automatically project object becomes the
自动投影的对象成为
prepaid access tokens from user networks
来自用户网络的预付费访问令牌
and
和
the rating of the standard is endpoint
标准的等级是终点
hero the configuration of the configuration
英雄配置
for the danube token contents of the
对于的多瑙河令牌内容
custom claims provider at plock's
plock的自定义索赔提供者
journey to the code in order to
前往代码以
mid-april information
4月中旬信息
the effects for the at you can find s
的效果，您可以找到
stuff on my guitar repository thomas
我的吉他资料库托马斯上的东西
home and blogger the motto of
家庭和博客作者的座右铭
pop duos before the exam technologies
流行二人考试前的技术
[Music]
[音乐]
that we can used end fourth
我们可以用第四位结束
german club the autumn sun keindorf
德国俱乐部秋日的太阳肯多夫
it becomes president in front of me cluster
在我面前成为总裁
explodes like disability information
爆炸像残疾信息
from other supporters maria the server
来自其他支持者的玛丽亚服务器
becomes
应
basically forwards events of the stairs
基本上转发楼梯事件
ski-club via games okraffka nobody
滑雪俱乐部通过游戏okraffka没人
miss broker in order to conversion
小姐经纪为了转换
professional data like you changes
像您这样的专业数据发生变化
profile
轮廓
we have greylock public eat eat
我们有灰发公众吃
love shot me information about what
爱向我射击了有关什么的信息
happened master just login
刚发生的主人刚登录
when she is still in here by humans
当她还被人类留在这里时
to the budget lures messages of walking
预算吸引步行信息
for user tests
用于用户测试
the data works via lockout lock out
数据通过锁定工作
the lookout messages with would give me a
与监视消息将给我一个
good people's performance offered messages
良好的人的表现提供了信息
if the jusos allowed the native
如果犹太人允许本地人
know of course b live video in hd
当然知道b现场高清视频
sport zdf de rossi the dashboard that
Sport zdf de rossi的仪表板
wars special metric after a new version
新版本后出现特别指标
got the one that got got to high tech
得到了一个高科技
Transporter on the pressing
压紧运输车
Information of the mq walking event
MQ步行活动信息
promotion events via dms via casting
通过dms通过投放促销活动
club extensions car window user changes
俱乐部扩展车窗用户更改
username profile information here as
用户名个人资料信息，此处为
jason based message of the gästeinformation
基于jason的gästeinformation消息
okay the user profile update performed by
好的，用户配置文件更新是由
the user eg otto the admin user betfair
用户，例如otto管理员用户betfair
user here is the network
用户在这里是网络
user profiles of people who do not
不这样做的人的用户个人资料
people you can add distributor user
可以添加分销商用户的人
profile page touchpad user conference
个人资料页面触摸板用户会议
manager of the address internet service
地址互联网服务经理
management on the tsv dress of zsc
zsc的tsv连衣裙的管理
klopp but can not believe it's just a
克洛普，但不敢相信这只是一个
matter of downloading distribution of
下载分配问题
Installing ricoh website is in you get
您可以安装ricoh网站
the same and construction &amp; rollinger
和建筑及压路机一样
localhost 3 yuki kozo celebrity daughter
localhost 3 yuki kozo名人女儿
images / getty conficker tend to get
图片/盖蒂迷惑倾向
started but what is common to use the
开始了，但是使用
standard of the images for production
制作图像的标准
because they have raised a lot of staff
因为他们培养了很多员工
audio codec equipment features of the
音频编解码器设备的功能
box is the city-center like the pace
盒子是城市中心般的步伐
of standards and the exorcist not
标准和驱魔人不是
possible to integrated management
可能进行整合管理
infrastructure so very much and storage
基础设施非常丰富
[Applause]
[鼓掌]
[Music]
[音乐]